<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dallas Attractions</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- General -->
    <string name="attraction_image_content_description">A photo showing the attraction</string>
    <string name="attraction_location_icon_description">A marker icon shown next to the attraction\'s address</string>
    <!-- SECTION 1: Downtown-->
    <string name="downtown_category">downtown</string>
    <!-- Downtown 1 -->
    <string name="downtown1_name">World Aquarium</string>
    <string name="downtown1_address">1801 N Griffin St, Dallas, TX 75202</string>
    <string name="downtown1_description">The Dallas World Aquarium is a for-profit aquarium
        and zoo located in the West End Historic District of downtown Dallas,
        Texas, USA.</string>
    <string name="downtown1_filename">downtown_aquarium</string>
    <!-- Downtown 2 -->
    <string name="downtown2_name">West End</string>
    <string name="downtown2_address">null</string>
    <string name="downtown2_description">The West End Historic District of Dallas, Texas,
        is a historic district that includes a 67.5-acre area in northwest downtown,
        generally north of Commerce, east of I-35E, west of Lamar and south of
        Woodall Rodgers Freeway.</string>
    <string name="downtown2_filename">downtown_west_end</string>
    <!-- Downtown 3 -->
    <string name="downtown3_name">Klyde Warren Park</string>
    <string name="downtown3_address">32°47′22″N 96°48′06″W</string>
    <string name="downtown3_description">Klyde Warren Park creates an urban green space constructed
        over a section of the below-grade Woodall Rodgers Freeway, for 3 blocks between Pearl
        Street and St. Paul Street. It provides connectivity to the city’s flourishing Arts
        District from other neighborhoods, brings together cultural events and experiences,
        and serves as a central public gathering space for Dallas residents and visitors to enjoy.</string>
    <string name="downtown3_filename">downtown_klyde_warren</string>
    <!-- Downtown 4 -->
    <string name="downtown4_name">John F. Kennedy Memorial</string>
    <string name="downtown4_address">646 Main St, Dallas, TX 75202</string>
    <string name="downtown4_description">The John Fitzgerald Kennedy Memorial is a monument
        to U.S. President John Fitzgerald Kennedy in the West End Historic District of downtown
        Dallas, Texas erected in 1970, and designed by noted architect Philip Johnson.</string>
    <string name="downtown4_filename">downtown_jfk_memorial</string>
    <!-- Downtown 5 -->
    <string name="downtown5_name">City Hall</string>
    <string name="downtown5_address">500 Marilla St, Dallas, TX 75201</string>
    <string name="downtown5_description">Dallas City Hall is the seat of Dallas municipal
        government, located at 1500 Marilla in the Government District of downtown
        Dallas, Texas</string>
    <string name="downtown5_filename">downtown_city_hall</string>
    <!-- SECTON 2: Museums -->
    <string name="museum_category">museums</string>
    <!-- Museum 1 -->
    <string name="museum1_name">Dallas Museum of Art</string>
    <string name="museum1_address">1717 N. Harwood, Dallas, TX</string>
    <string name="museum1_description">The museum collection is made up of more than
        24,000 objects, dating from the third millennium BC to the present day.
        It is also defined by its dynamic exhibition policy and
        award-winning educational programs.</string>
    <string name="museum1_filename">museum_dma</string>
    <!-- Museum 2 -->
    <string name="museum2_name">Old Red Museum of Dallas County History &amp; Culture</string>
    <string name="museum2_address">100 S Houston St, Dallas, TX 75202</string>
    <string name="museum2_description">Dramatic 1890 red sandstone courthouse exhibiting city
        annals &amp; artifacts plus events &amp; programs.</string>
    <string name="museum2_filename">museum_old_red</string>
    <!-- Museum 3 -->
    <string name="museum3_name">Perot Museum of Nature and Science</string>
    <string name="museum3_address">2201 N Field St, Dallas, TX 75201</string>
    <string name="museum3_description">The Perot Museum of Nature and Science consists of two
        campuses: the primary campus located in Victory Park, and a secondary
        campus in Fair Park. It features eleven exhibit halls and including 3D simulations,
        hands-on activities, interactive kiosks and educational games.</string>
    <string name="museum3_filename">museum_perot</string>
    <!-- Museum 4 -->
    <string name="museum4_name">Trammell &amp;  Margaret Crow Collection of Asian Art</string>
    <string name="museum4_address">2010 Flora St, Dallas, TX 75201</string>
    <string name="museum4_description">The Trammell &amp; Margaret Crow Collection of Asian Art,
        also known as the Crow Collection of Asian Art, is a museum dedicated to the arts and
        cultures of China, Japan, India and Southeast Asia.</string>
    <string name="museum4_filename">museum_asian</string>
    <!-- Museum 5 -->
    <string name="museum5_name">Meadows Museum</string>
    <string name="museum5_address">5900 Bishop Boulevard Dallas, TX 75275</string>
    <string name="museum5_description">The Meadows Museum is a division of the Southern
        Methodist University Meadows School of the Arts. It houses one of the largest and
        most comprehensive collections of Spanish art outside of Spain, with works dating
        from the 10th to the 20th century. It includes masterpieces by some of the world\'s
        greatest painters: El Greco, Velázquez, Ribera, Murillo, Goya, Miró, Sorolla,
        and Picasso.</string>
    <string name="museum5_filename">museum_meadow</string>
    <!-- SECTION 3: Trails -->
    <string name="trail_category">trails</string>
    <!-- Trail 1 -->
    <string name="trail1_name">Katy Trail</string>
    <string name="trail1_address">null</string>
    <string name="trail1_description">The Katy Trail is a jogging, walking, inline skating,
        and bicycling path that runs through the Uptown and Oak Lawn areas of Dallas,
        following the path of the old Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad, which was known
        as MKT or the Katy.</string>
    <string name="trail1_filename">trail_katy</string>
    <!-- Trail 2 -->
    <string name="trail2_name">Santa Fe Trestle</string>
    <string name="trail2_address">null</string>
    <string name="trail2_description">The steel portion of  the bridge was originally built
        in 1926 and served as a main artery for the AT&amp;SF Railroad in Dallas.
        Some old signs along the old right of way can still be found in the overgrowth.
        In 1985 the trestle was burned in an overnight fire destroying over half the structure.</string>
    <string name="trail2_filename">trail_santa_fe_trestle</string>
    <!-- Trail 3 -->
    <string name="trail3_name">Sata Fe Trail</string>
    <string name="trail3_address">null</string>
    <string name="trail3_description">With a length of 5.3 miles, the Santa Fe Trail extends
        the continuous trail corridor that begins in far northern Dallas with the Preston Ridge
        Trail so that the corridor now ends at the doorstep of downtown Dallas -
        a distance of over 20 miles.</string>
    <string name="trail3_filename">trail_santa_fe</string>
    <!-- Trail 4 -->
    <string name="trail4_name">White Rock</string>
    <string name="trail4_address">null</string>
    <string name="trail4_description">White Rock Lake is a reservoir located in north-east Dallas.
        The lake was formed by damming White Rock Creek, which today widens into the lake before
        continuing south out of the spillway and emptying into the Trinity River
        as MKT or the Katy. The lake is surrounded by White Rock Lake Park,
        which features a 9.33 mile (15 km) trail for hiking, running and bicycling,
        the Bath House Cultural Center and the Dallas Arboretum and Botanical Garden.
        There are several fishing piers and sailing is permitted.</string>
    <string name="trail4_filename">trail_whiterock</string>
    <!-- Trail 5 -->
    <string name="trail5_name">Cedar Ridge Nature Center</string>
    <string name="trail5_address">null</string>
    <string name="trail5_description">The Cedar Ridge Nature Preserve is a scenic,
        rich in wildlife, slice of hill country.
        Formerly the Dallas Nature Center, the preserve spans 600 acres between Mountain
        Creek Parkway and FM 1382, a short 20 minutes from downtown Dallas.
        The natural habitat is jointly owned by the City of Dallas and Dallas
        County and features native trees, grasses, and wildflowers, displaying
        the natural beauty of the area.</string>
    <string name="trail5_filename">trail_cedar_ridge</string>
    <!-- SECTION 4: Food -->
    <string name="food_category">food</string>
    <!--Food 1-->
    <string name="food1_name">Marie\'s Mantle</string>
    <string name="food1_address">1701 S Lamar St, Dallas, TX 75215</string>
    <string name="food1_description">Marie\’s Mantle creates and delivers diverse, healthy
        and familiar cuisine that you can truly enjoy. We cater to the “everyday person” who
        enjoys being active, has a social &amp; family life and a career. At the end of the day,
        you simply want to lead a healthy, fulfilling life.</string>
    <string name="food1_filename">food_maries_mantle</string>
    <!--Food 2-->
    <string name="food2_name">Central Market</string>
    <string name="food2_address">5750 E Lovers Ln, Dallas, TX 75206</string>
    <string name="food2_description">Try a sumptuous selection of everything edible, for starters.
        We go straight to the source to bring you some of the finest foods Texas and the rest
        of the world have to offer. With hundreds of cheeses, thousands of wines, acres of
        produce, and aisles of experts, Central Market is for everyone really into food.</string>
    <string name="food2_filename">food_central_market</string>
    <!--Food 3-->
    <string name="food3_name">El Corazon de Tejas</string>
    <string name="food3_address">110 W Davis St, Dallas, TX 75208</string>
    <string name="food3_description">Regional Mexican cooking &amp; seasonal beverage specialties in a
        classic space with vintage decor.</string>
    <string name="food3_filename">food_corazon_tejas</string>
    <!--Food 4-->
    <string name="food4_name">Truck Yard</string>
    <string name="food4_address">5624 Sears St, Dallas, TX 75206</string>
    <string name="food4_description">Complex housing food trucks in an expansive,
        retro outdoor space with treehouse &amp; trailer bars.</string>
    <string name="food4_filename">food_truck_yard</string>
    <!--Food 5-->
    <string name="food5_name">Eatzi\'s Market</string>
    <string name="food5_address">3403 OAK LAWN AVE. Dallas, TX 75219</string>
    <string name="food5_description">Eatzi\'s Market &amp; Bakery is a chain of bakery, gourmet
        takeout markets, and restaurants, created by Philip J. Romano. It was based in the
        Dallas–Fort Worth metroplex, and proposes high end products. Four locations
        in Dallas remain open. </string>
    <string name="food5_filename">food_eat_zis</string>

</resources>
